{
    "subject": "resource/Patrick_Boyle,_8th_Earl_of_Glasgow",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow",
    "human_readable": "Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow is labeled as 'Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9372768402099609,
            "question": "Who succeeded Patrick Boyle as the Earl of Glasgow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.891806960105896,
            "question": "What number Earl was Patrick Boyle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8080297112464905,
            "question": "Who was Patrick Boyle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7071730494499207,
            "question": "What is the full name of Patrick Boyle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6594938635826111,
            "question": "Were there any famous events or periods during Patrick Boyle's life as Earl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6001725196838379,
            "question": "Was Patrick Boyle a nobleman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5905359983444214,
            "question": "To what family did Patrick Boyle belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5707277059555054,
            "question": "What title did Patrick Boyle hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.558022677898407,
            "question": "What were some of the responsibilities associated with being the Earl of Glasgow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2730315923690796,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the history of the Earls of Glasgow?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow is labeled as 'Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5178_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the responsibilities associated with being the Earl of Glasgow?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5178_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What title did Patrick Boyle hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5178_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what family did Patrick Boyle belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5178_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5178_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5178_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5178_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5178_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5178_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5178_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5178_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5178_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5178_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5178_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention anything related to writing or being an author. The only information provided about Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow is his background as a nobleman and politician, but there is no indication that he is a writer or author, let alone specifically \"Pat Frank\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context information clearly refers to an individual named \"Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow\" and provides details about his political and noble roles. Therefore, the statement that Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow is labeled as 'Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow' is accurate according to the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the context information reveals multiple sources with different birth dates for Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow (June 18, 1874 and June 18 is not mentioned in other information), which contradicts the idea that \"Patrick Boyle, 8th Earl of Glasgow\" is a singular, fixed label.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}